amway.sg 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Amway Singapore

Protecting Your Information  
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site, and to promptly advise Amway if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. Per our password policy you are required to change your password every year to prevent unauthorized access. Be sure to make note of your new password and keep the information in a safe place. For your security, do not share your password with others. Because your identification number and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your identification number and password.

Amway also strongly advises that current anti-virus, anti-spyware software is run on computers you use and that operating systems are kept up to date.

Use of Cookies on This Site  
A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a website to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Cookies also enable an internet retailer like Amway to keep track of a consumer's electronic "shopping cart" before completing a purchase. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read our cookies, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Google Chrome) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some website features that will not be available to you, and some web pages may not display properly.

To support the personalized features of our Site (such as your country and language codes, electronic shopping cart, and other ordering and browsing functions), we must send a cookie to your computer's hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered Site user. We do not, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the web.

Use of Active-X and Java Applets On This Site  
Active-X programs and Java Applets are executable programs that can be transferred to your computer's hard drive to cause your computer to perform functions concerning your visit to a website. 

Our Site does not transfer any Active-X programs or Java Applets to your computer's hard drive.

Use of Third-Party Media and Research Companies  
Our Site may run limited third-party ads only for those Merchant and Services Partners with whom we maintain linking agreements. In addition, we may use third-party media and research companies to place ads for us on other parties' websites. 

Links to Other Websites  
Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

We maintain contractual agreements with all of our Merchant and Services Partners, which require them to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement. When you enter a Partner Store from our Site, we provide them only with your identification number for purposes of introducing you. In return, the Partner Store shares with us any purchases you make from their websites in order for us to assign proper credit to you and to your servicing ABOs.

Children's Privacy Protection  
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. We abide by the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and other relevant laws. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data. You must be at least 18 years old as a customer or qualify as an ABO to be on our Site. 

Changes To This Statement  
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Security Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Security Statement has changed. If any changes materially affect the use of Personally Identifiable Information previously provided to us, we will obtain your consent prior to the retroactive application of any material changes. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Security Statement in effect at the time of use. 

Contact Us  
If you have any concerns about your security using this Site or about this Security Statement, please send an email to myhelpdesk@amway.com or call Customer Service at 03-79462800. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention. 

Updated and effective August 31,2011.  
©2013 Amway, Malaysia, all rights reserved
